{
    "id": "860542a3c5e54fa29bcb069552e8eef6",
    "title": "Do And Make Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He made me …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wait",
                "to wait"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dd89aaf5b9874bb2a11de26995deb56d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………… the whole story.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "made to repeat",
                "was made repeating",
                "was made to repeat"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6b1181dc79d64217ae747e75cde03040"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t speak French well, but I can ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "make myself understand",
                "make me understand",
                "make myself understood"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "551c0d1758284603a474717794bc7994"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had to shout to ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "make me heard",
                "make myself heard",
                "make myself hear"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1266601926da48779937c46f58aaf377"
        },
        {
            "question": "Paper is made …………………. wood.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "out of",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "adaa520c8cf9448b8c8f5dcb2bb74621"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is time to ………………… the accounts.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "make",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "045beab40b5b496a807f5196206226aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "He likes ……………….. nothing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "doing",
                "making"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5e9034d228d54636b420b2ff1da209d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is old enough to ……………. her own bed now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "make",
                "do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f3af5092bded42df94786120ddc6ffde"
        },
        {
            "question": "She lost her money. I wasn’t surprised that she …………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "make"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3c34893e7a2b417dab71e1dd3f0ee5a7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ever made wine ………………. blackberries?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fdadae8613a14ebe8e74638a50bfecc3"
        }
    ]
}